Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office records, 1941-1990; RG0055 Series 50; 15 Linear feet (Box 10, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    The Trinidad Steelband, Rafael Puyana Harpsichordist, Murray Lowis Dance Company, Ballet Spectacular
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Canterbury Tales, Washington Hospital Center School of Nursing Commencement, Commencement of the Frank W. Ballou High School, Argentine Folk Mass, 25th Anniversary Concert Montgomery County Youth Orchestra, The National Ballet
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Abbey Road, The Paul Sanasardo Dance Company, Inter-American Music Festival
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Dinah Christie and Tom Kneebone Non-Stop Britain, Ballet Theatre Contemporain, Ballet Company of Washington Coppelia, Les Ballets Africains
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Inward to the Sea, Mummen Schanz, Casa Cuba, UpBeat, The Nutcracker, Roy Radin Vaudeville Revue
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Itzhak Perlman, Commencement of the University Hospital Center, Festival of the Nations, Commencement Exercises for the Immaculate Conception Academy
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    George Washington University Orchestra
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Washington Performing Arts Society, Graduation Ceremony for Bishop Ireton High School, Concerts in Schools Festival, Kiss Me Kate, Medical School Follies, Martha Graham Center of Contemporary Dance Inc
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Capitol Ballet Company, Festival of the Nations, Mignon, National Symphony Orchestra Rigoletto, Alice in OD Land
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Inward to the Sea, French Contemporary Art Festival, The Howard Roberts Chorale, Washington Performing Arts Society
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Sontraud Speidel, The Crucible, Washington Civic Opera Association, American Bicentennial Opera, Conference for Spiritual Freedom
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Jan Van Dyke and Dancers, National Symphony Orchestra, B'Nai B'Rith Convocation of Thanksgiving, Commencement Bishop Ireton High School, Washington Performing Arts Society
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Inward to the Sea, Roman State Orchestra
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    The Gospel Chorus, D.C. Youth Orchestra, The Barber of Seville, The Mecca Melodiers
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    La Traviata, National Lyric Opera Company, The Washington Civic Opera Association, The Karmapa of Tibet
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    The Elixir of Love, GWU Opening Convocation, MSTISLAV ROSTROPOVICH, Madame Butterfly, Joffrey II Dancers, Washington Ballet Nutcracker, Golden Gala
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    United States Marine Band, Washington Civic Opera Association, Gay Men's Chorus of DC, The Gypsy Baron
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Holly Near and Ronnie Gilbert In Concert, Washington's Underwater Festival, OnStage!, Washington Ballet, Law Revue Class Reunion, The Sydney Youth Chamber Orchestra
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    New Music America, Tango Festival, Medical School Follies, The Eternal Flame, Rainbow Terrace Calypso, Friday Night Live
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    D.C. Chapter Gospel Workshop of America, Inc.
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Lisner at Noon
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    The Washington Ballet-Nutcracker
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Lisner at Noon, School Without Walls Commencement
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Cuban Folklore, A Prairie Home Companion, Caribbean Festivals Inc., National Symphony Orchestra, Edward Villella, Indian Cultural Association, The Day of Hope, The American Light Opera Company, The Christmas Revels
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Washington Performing Arts Society, The United Holy Land Fund, The President's Own Salute to Patriotism, Agustin Anievas, The Nutcracker
  - Usher Assignments, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Usher Assignments, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Usher Assignments, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Usher Assignments, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Usher Assignments, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Usher Assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Usher Assignments, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Usher Assignments, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Usher Assignments, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Usher Assignments, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Usher Assignments, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Usher Assignments, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Usher Assignments, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Usher Assignments, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Usher Assignments, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Usher Assignments, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Usher Assignments, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Usher Assignments, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Usher Assignments, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Usher Assignments, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Calendar, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Commencement, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Labor Contracts, 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Lisner Buildings and Performers-photos, negatives, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Miscellaneous Correspondence with Frank Early, 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Miscellaneous programs, 1969-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium-National Ballet photos and memos, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Seating Guides, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Tickets, 1964-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Work Records (sampling), 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Audio tapes, RG0055 Series 51; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series includes eight 10 inch reel to reel audio tapes of RKO radio shows.
  Formerly ACC# 980
- Programs, posters, 1999-2001; RG0055 Series 52; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes programs and posters for events from 1999-2001.
  Formerly ACC#1011
  - Beyond Me, 11/10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Fall Schedule, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - The Legend of Bagger Vance, 11/01/2000 (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - Favorite Songs of Yesteryear, 11/04/2000 (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - The Little Angels, 01/27/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - A Symphonic Celebration, 02/08/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
  - LaTirana/Sanlucar, 02/01/2001-02/09/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.7)
  - Sofrito, 02/10/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.8)
  - Aurora/2001, 02/15/2001-02/16/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.9)
  - North Korean Music Festival, 02/22/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Masters of Persian Music, 02/25/2001 (Box 1, Folder 1.11)
  - Law Revue XXIII, 03/03/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Holi Rangeela, 03/10/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Maria de Buenes Aires, 03/16/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Harmony Sweepstakes, 03/17/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - 300 Tenors, 03/24/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Medical School Follies, 03/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - American Youth Orchestra, 04/01/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - No Fair Tale, 04/04/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Jolina and Gabby, 04/07/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Mazhar Fuat Ozkan, 04/13/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Film Fest DC 2001, 04/17/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Il Pirata, 04/20/2001-04/22/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - A Centennial Journal, 04/20/2001-04/22/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - GW Spring Symphony, 04/29/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Morning, Noon and Night, 05/05/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Upakar, 05/06/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Peter Schikele, 05/11/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/18/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Graduate School of Education and Human Development Awards, 05/19/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.5)
  - Columbian School of Arts and Sciences Celebration, 05/19/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.6)
  - School of Public Health and Health Services Commencement, 05/19/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.7)
  - Medical School Commencement, 05/20/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.8)
  - Washington Ballet, 05/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.9)
  - Metro DC Dance Awards, 06/05/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Alabina, 06/09/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Georgetown Day School Graduation, 06/10/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - School Without Walls Graduation, 06/12/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - School of Engineering and Apprenticeship Program Opening, 06/25/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.5)
  - Hermanos Gaitan-Castro, 07/06/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.6)
  - Carey Memorial, 07/25/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.7)
  - Colonial Inauguration Closing, 07/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.8)
  - CI Capital Steps, 07/2001 (Box 1, Folder 5.9)
  - Aurora/2001, 02/15/2001-02/16/2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Youssou N'Dour, 11/21/2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Masters of Persian Music, 02/25/2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cheb Mami, 07/18/2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hermanos Gaitan-Castro, 07/06/2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Metro DC Dance Awards, 06/05/2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - GLAAD Media Awards, 05/12/2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alga Yagnik, 05/05/2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Our Lady Peace, 05/02/2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - San Luis Obispo Symphony, 04/27/2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pablo Milanes, 04/15/2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mazhar Fuat Ozkan, 04/13/2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Holi Rangeela, 03/10/2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Maria de Buenes Aires, 03/16/2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - North Korean Music Festival, 02/22/2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Little Angels, 01/27/2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Millennium Show, 10/07/2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rahat Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, 09/24/2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Paolo Conte, 02/24/2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Programs, pamphlets, posters, 2001-2002; RG0055 Series 53; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes programs, pamphlets, and posters from performances and events in lisner auditorium from 2001-02.
  Formerly ACC#1034
  - Usher Applications, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Danilo Perez and Motherland Project, 09/22/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Arturo Sandoval, 10/11/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - An Evening with Dave Brubeck, 10/18/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - TrainWreck Dance Company, 10/20/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Tripitaka Koreana, 10/27/2001 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Old, New, Borrowed, and Blue, 11/01/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - RAAS Chaos, 11/02/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Harvest of Harmony, 11/03/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Gala Tribute to Ignacy Jan Paderewski, 11/05/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Lila Downs, 11/10/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Veteran's Day and the West Point Bicentennial, 11/11/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - Mickey Hart & Bembe Orishe, 11/14/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - Papin Sisters in Concert, 11/16/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Franz Liszt: A Celebration, 11/17/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
  - The Benjamin Caper Memorial Lecture, 11/19/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - The Christmas Revels, 11/30/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3.11)
  - In Search of the Great White Tiger, 12/11/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - An Evening of Music, 01/19/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Flamenco Festival, 01/24/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 01/31/2002-02/02/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Urban Tap, 02/09/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.5)
  - GW Wind Ensemble and Band, 02/20/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.6)
  - Knock, Knock, Anybody Home?, 02/21/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.7)
  - Kronos Quartet, 02/21/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.8)
  - Freedom Fighters, 02/23/2002 (Box 1, Folder 4.9)
    2 program
  - Law Revue, 03/02/2002 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Shalom Hanoch, 03/03/2002 (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Washington International Competition, 03/10/2002 (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Wizard of Oz, 03/22/2002 (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - City at Peace, 04/03/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - International Night, 04/12/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - 15th Anniversary Concert, 04/14/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - DC Film Fest, 04/17/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.4)
  - Soul of the West, 04/24/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.5)
  - Emel Sayin, 04/27/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6.6)
  - Brigham Young University Ballroom Dancers, 04/27/2002-05/11/2002 (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/17/2002 (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Commencement 2002 - School of Public Health and Health Services, 05/18/2002 (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - Night at the Opera II, 05/19/2002 (Box 1, Folder 7.4)
  - Mexican Journeys, 06/01/2002 (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
    2 programs and 2 posters
  - Sheila E and the E Train, 06/08/2002 (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Georgetown Day School Graduation, 06/09/2002 (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
  - School Without Walls Graduation, 06/11/2002 (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
  - Undated Programs, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    National Heritage Fellowships
  - Veteran's Day and the West Point Bicentennial, 11/11/2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Romeros, 10/13/2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 01/31/2002-02/02/2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Youssou N'Dour, 04/16/2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Franz Liszt: A Celebration, 11/17/2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mickey Hart & Bembe Orishe, 11/14/2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rhythms of the Desert, 11/14/2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Los Fakires, 11/20/2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Soul of the West, 09/25/2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Stepping into Unity, 02/23/2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Emel Sayin, 04/27/2002-05/26/2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rahat Nusrat Fatah Ali Khan Qawwal & Party, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sounds of the Ganges River, 10/21/2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    4 posters
  - TrainWreck Dance Company, 10/20/2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Programs, pamphlets, and posters, 2002-2003; RG0055 Series 54; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 2)
  This series includes programs, pamphlets, and posters from performances and events in Lisner auditorium from 2002-03.
  Formerly ACC#1041
  - L'Ormindo, 08/11/2002 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 08/22/2002 (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - America Through the CBS Eye, 09/03/2002 (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - National Heritage Fellowship, 09/20/2002 (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Masters of Persian Music, 10/13/2002 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Paul Anka, 10/17/2002 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - GW Symphony Fall Concert, 10/27/2002 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Moein, Mansour, Ranna, 11/09/2002 (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
    1 program, 1 picture
  - Christmas Revels, 12/06/2002 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Peter Dvorsky, 02/05/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
    2 programs, 2 flyers
  - Law Revue, 03/01/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - Code Pink, 03/07/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - Company USA, 03/15/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
    1 flyer
  - Fred Hersch, 04/05/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - David Sedaris, 04/09/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.11)
  - Afro-Cuban All Stars, 04/26/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2.12)
  - Misia, 11/03/2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Susan Tedeschi, 04/02/2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chava Alberstein, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Programs, pamphlets, posters, 2002-2004; RG0055 Series 55; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 2, Map-folder 1)
  This series includes programs, pamphlets, and posters from performances and events in lisner auditorium from 2002-04.
  Formerly ACC#1065
  - Ash Wednesday, 03/05/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Newman Catholic Center
  - Holi Rangeela, 03/08/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Indian Students Association. 2 programs
  - The Company Hits USA Tour, 03/15/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: A and E Productions. 2 programs
  - Show Face, 03/27/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: City at Peace. 2 programs
  - GW Follies, 04/04/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences. 2 programs
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra, 04/12/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Lisner Auditorium. 2 programs
  - Basile: Road to the Olympics World Tour, 05/03/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Sigma Entertainment. 2 programs
  - GSEHD: Awards Ceremony, 05/17/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: George Washington University. 2 programs
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/16/2003 (Box 2)
  - Spring Commencement Spring 2003, School of Public Health and Health Services, 05/17/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: School of Public Health and Health Services. 2 programs
  - Commencement, 05/18/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: School of Medicine and Health Sciences. 2 programs
  - Parissa and Dastan Ensemble, 05/25/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Iranian Cultural Foundation Bahar's Volunteer Group. 2 posters
  - Tenth Season Gala, 08/08/2003-08/10/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Opera International. 1 postcard and 1 program. Performances on Aug. 8 and 10
  - Science and Engineering Apprentice Program: Closing Program, 08/15/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GWU and School of Engineering and Science and the Dept. of Defense
  - Metro DC Dance Awards, 09/08/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Mason Rhynes Productions. 2 programs
  - Spanish Harlem Orchestra, 09/13/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: The Smithsonian Associates. 2 programs
  - Induction Ceremony, The National Society of Collegiate Scholars, 10/16/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: The National Society of Collegiate Scholars. 2 programs
  - Ballet Boyz, 10/21/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Washington Performing Arts Society. 2 programs
  - Glenn Miller Orchestra, 02/05/2003 (Box 2)
  - A College Band Collage, 02/12/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GW Band. 2 programs
  - Outclassed: Law Revue, 02/28/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GWU Law School. 2 programs
  - Bye Bye Birdie Programs, 03/26/2004-03/28/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC
  - Bye Bye Birdie Posters, 03/26/2004-03/28/2004 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC. 2 posters
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra, 04/03/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Lisner Auditorium. 2 postcards and 1 program
  - Whirling Dervishes of Rumi, 04/10/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Rumi Forum for Interfaith Dialogue. 2 programs
  - Dialogues of the Carmelites, 07/30/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Opera International. 1 postcard
  - L'Ormindo, 08/09/2002-08/11/2002 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Opera International. Performances on Aug 9 and 11
  - Gurdas Maan, 08/16/2002 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: DVD Sound and Film, Inc.
  - Facundo Cabral, 08/17/2002 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Latinshow Productions
  - National Heritage Fellowships Concert and Celebration: Master Folk and Traditional Artists, 09/20/2002 (Box 2)
    Promoter: National Endowment for the Arts
  - Shaolin Wheel of Life, 01/24/2003 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: House of Blues Concerts
  - Algerian National Ballet, 03/05/2003 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Algerian Embassy. 2 posters
  - Holi Rangeela, 03/08/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Indian Students Association
  - The Company Hits USA Tour, 03/15/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: A and E Productions
  - A Spring Exchange Concert, 04/06/2003 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Lisner Auditorium
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra, 04/12/2003 (Box 2)
  - Parissa and Dastan Ensemble, 05/23/2003 (Box 2, Map-folder 1)
  - Dariush and Michael, 06/07/2003 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Harmony Group
  - Tenth Season Gala, 08/08/2003-08/10/2003 (Box 2, Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Opera International. Performances on Aug. 8 and 10
  - Metro DC Dance Awards, 09/08/2003 (Box 2)
    Promoter: Mason Rhynes Productions
  - Outclassed: Law Revue, 02/28/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GWU Law School
  - Holi Rangeela, 03/06/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: GW Indian Student Association
  - Whirling Dervishes of Rumi, 04/10/2004 (Map-folder 1, Box 2)
    Promoter: Rumi Forum for Interfaith Dialogue. 2 posters
  - Bela Fleck and Edgar Meyer, 05/20/2004 (Box 2)
    Promoter: AEG Live
  - Road to Victory, 05/28/2004-05/29/2004 (Map-folder 1)
    Promoter: Road to Victory. 2 posters
  - Code Pink, Circa 2002-2004; Series 55 (Map-folder 1)
- Posters, 1999-2009; RG0055 Series 56; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of posters from performances at Lisner Auditorium. The materials range in date from 1999-2009.
  - Program - Two Maestros, 04/16/2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    with Pundit Shiv Kumar Sharma and Ustad Zakir Hussain
  - "Invitation to Dance" Gay Men's Chorus of DC, 04/11/1999-04/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ideas Happen, 09/09/2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    contest presented by Visa
  - Sing-A-Long Sound of Music, 10/16/2004-10/17/2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Putumayo presents: "Latinas: Women of Latin America", 10/22/2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Pankaj Udhas, 03/06/2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Men! Men? Men... Gay Men's Chorus of DC, 03/19/2005-03/20/2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blind Boys of Alabama, 04/02/2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ismael Lo, 04/07/2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Comedy Central presents: "Dave Attell and the Insomniac Tour", 04/29/2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Shahrokh, 04/30/2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Khaled and Friends, 07/01/2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Bolo Moye Dolle/Unity is Power": 26th Annual National African Dance and Drum Festival, Kankouran West African Dance Company, 09/05/2009; RG0055 Series 56 (Map-folder 1, Poster 1)
  - "The Christmas Revels: In Celebration of the Winter Solstice.", 12/05/2009-12/13/2009 (Map-folder 1, Poster 2-3)
    General
    2 copies of 11" x 17" posters for "The Christmas Revels: In Celebration of the Winter Solstice." Italian Renaissance Music, Dance, and Drama. December 5-6 and 11-13 2009.
  - Comedian Bill Burr (autographed), 19 November 2010; 2010 (Map-folder 1, Poster 4)
- Events and performances, 1946-2003; RG0055 Series 57; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains correspondence, brochures, news releases, newspaper clippings, proposal, invitation, newsletters, and flyers. They range in date from 1946 to 2003. They concern performances, Lisner Auditorium's history, renovation, schedules of events, and segregation.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Buildings -- Lisner Auditorium -- Art Work, 1944-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium, 02/03/1952-03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium Schedule of Events, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium - Segregation controversy of 1946, 10/10/1946-05/02/1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium - Segregation controversy, 1946 (Gift of Ruth Horland Wells 3/01) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Flyers, programs, memorabilia, 2000-2008; RG0055 Series 58; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, pamphlets, and posters from performances and events in lisner auditorium from 2000-06. Also included is a memorabilia cup from the 175th GW anniversary. Inside the cup is a sample of Lisner's old carpeting.
  - Posters, 2003-2006 (Box 2)
  - America the Fabulous: Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC Kicks Off Capital Pride 2008 (Oversize-folder 1, Item 1)
  - Ralphie May, 2008 (Oversize-folder 1, Item 2)
  - "Spring Fling" Concert, 2008 (Oversize-folder 1, Item 3)
  - Programs and Schedules, 2004-2007; Series 59 (Box SHARED 2, Folder 12)